I'm with the Kelly White Team, and today we're going to tell you how to buy a house.
Okay, now I'm going to talk about the exclusive buyer/broker agreement.
That's a big fancy word for loyalty agreement.
What's going to happen sometimes in most cases your realtor is going to ask you to sign this.
Don't be afraid.
All it's saying is saying that you are going to be loyal to me.
I'm going to show you these houses, you're going to use me, you're not going to call other realtors.
If you're interested in another property, you're going to call me to show it to you.
All it is it's saying I as a realtor, am trusting you.
I'm taking my time.
I'm spending my dollars, I'm spending my hours finding you your perfect home.
All this is saying is that you're going to be respectful of our relationship and not stray.
Don't you stray, that's all it's saying.
And it doesn't cost you anything.
It isn't a contract.
It is legally binding, but it's all spelled out.
All it's saying its just a loyalty agreement.
It's saying you're going to respect me as a real estate professional, sign it.